Brought. fixed and synced by:
Yoav1610
I'm sorry about Eli.
You would've acted like me.
What? Shoot a person in the back?
The question is whether we can trust him.
- Yes. I believe so.
He stayed behind. he didn't run
even though he had a chance.
I think it's smart of you
to hide your brother from Hamas.
The Frenchman talked.
Turns out they fled the camp in Syria.
They're planning tonight to enter the country
through the Jordan Valley.
And you think Doron is part
of the group they'll try to smuggle in?
Steve. there's an indication
they're going to smuggle a group of terrorists
through the Jordan Valley.
and there's a chance Doron is one of them.
I need you in the field.
I'm sorry. Said. There's no authorization.
It comes from the leadership.
I arranged everything. changed contacts.
targets. Everything's good. Why...
Enough! This is not up for discussion.
We're done here.
This will be enough for you
to get back to Europe.
Today we set out
on an operation of heroes.
Said doesn't need anyone's approval.
Said will make us all heroes of
Palestine.
I was unfair to you. sorry.
You have the right to be angry with me
after what I did.
It was his choice.
This is war.
Shitty things happen in wars.
Split into cells and get into
the vehicles. quick.
Amir. Anne. let's go. you're with me.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Don't worry. they're just checking
the license plates.
Are we in Israel?
No. we're in Jordan.
- Jordan?
It's much easier to enter from here.
The border is long. very flat.
and there are many holes in the fence.
It's okay. you can go back to sleep.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Okay. listen up.
from here we'll continue on foot
into Israeli territory.
We need to be very
careful.
Yalla. we don't want delays.
They dragged you all the way here?
What's up. Danino?
- How's it going?
Last time I saw you
you were peeing into a bag. Where is it?
Thank God. I got off it.
Where's that damn Gabi?
What? - We estimate the terrorists
will cross the border tonight.
That means we head out now.
We have patrols along the entire sector.
I need you to be very alert
in your section.
Operational driving.
That means at least 20 meters between
vehicles. Don't ride their ass.
You have eyes from above. I'll be
in contact with you on the line. - Done.
Can I get coffee first?
- Yeah. a pastry too. Yalla. yalla.
Connect me. please.
So what? How about you?
About what?
How are you?
You're asking how I'm doing. like?
- Yeah.
Shit.
How about you? How do you feel?
Same.
Great. we shared feelings. Now
let me concentrate.
Does everyone cross here?
The less we know. the safer
we'll be.
Gabi. I'm spotting movement.
Steve. do you copy?
- Copy. over.
A few hundred meters north of you
there's a visual on hostiles.
- Roger. copy.
We're on the way.
Kfir. do you copy?
- Copy. over.
Close the southern route. so they
don't get past us there. - Roger. copy.
Get down. get down.
Steve. they're 50 meters east.
Steve. they've stopped moving.
Steve. what's going on?
Open your eyes. they're right in front of you.
There. I've spotted them.
Get up. get up.
Hands up.
You. lie on the ground.
Yalla. quick!
Who are you? What are you doing here?
We're crossing over to work.
The people you're looking for
took the southern roads.
What do you mean?
Hamas.
They already crossed from the
south. around Jericho.
How many people were there?
A lot. Almost 20.
Steve.
Steve. what's going on?
Just some illegal border-crossers.
The terrorists came in through Jericho.
Goddammit. that lowlife.
Habibi.
- Our sheikh.
Welcome. may your arrival be safe.
Praise be to God. I've returned.
How many made it?
Half of them. Some are still on the way.
They took difficult routes.
but they're all in Israel.
That's happy news.
- Praise be to God.
Let's go up. we can't stay here.
Come. Please.
Nice work.
Go rest.
An important day awaits us tomorrow.
I got this from Said.
Seems he sins in secret.
I couldn't sleep either.
How strange to know when you'll die. right?
Are you sure it'll happen tomorrow?
- Aren't you?
Sorry. I just have mixed
feelings about leaving tomorrow
and you're the only one I can talk
to without being afraid.
What about Maher's path?
Don't say that.
So you're just afraid to die?
I wish this whole messed-up thing
never happened.
I just imagine not seeing
my family again...
I hope you'll see them.
In this world or the next.
Yes.
Everything okay?
Yeah. it's a bit tight. but yes.
This is the trigger.
To activate it
you need to press this switch.
As long as it's off
you don't need to worry.
When it's on. pressing the top
button will activate the belt.
Understood?
Thank you for doing this for us.
May Allah protect you.
Okay. listen up.
The working assumption is that dozens of terrorists
with a European appearance
are hiding in the West Bank. ready to move out.
These are fighters who underwent training.
they're trained. determined to act
and to die if necessary.
Unfortunately. we didn't get a clear enough
picture regarding the attack target.
only that it's
a particularly strategic and sensitive place.
Everyone. we're entering
sensitive and charged days.
Dozens of events. ceremonies. gatherings
for Memorial Day and Independence Day.
I need peak alertness
from each and every one of you
so they pass safely. Is that clear?
In the name of Allah. the Most Gracious. the Most Merciful.
- In the name of Allah. the Most Gracious. the Most Merciful.
The Europeans have proven themselves so far.
Let them continue that way.
If you suspect you're being followed.
don't take risks.
The smugglers will take you
to an area near the Old City.
People start gathering there
around 6:00 PM.
and we'll begin to act exactly
at 7:30 PM.
The VIPs will already be there
and the plaza will be full of people.
Understood?
Understood.
- Good.
Whoever of you wants to say goodbye to their family.
let them do it now.
Keep it a short call. don't go into
details.
May Allah be with you.
Amir. everything okay?
Yes.
I'm thinking about what to say to my family.
Don't overthink it.
say what's in your heart.
Here you go. habibi.
Thank you. habibi.
Hello.
- Hello. Uncle Khaled. how are you?
Talk.
Talk. I'm listening.
- I missed you very much.
Listen to me carefully. five vehicles are leaving
Tubas from the "Al-Quds" school.
In each vehicle. four terrorists.
the Europeans with explosive belts.
The target is the ceremony at the Western Wall.
Now write down the
vehicles carefully. - Writing.
White Kia. burgundy Daihatsu.
white Kangoo. blue Chevrolet.
and a gray Outlander.
Got it? - Got it.
- Now hurry and go after them.
And don't call this number.
I'm deleting the call.
Yalla. see you.
I have to go. I'm in a hurry.
Wait. Doron. which vehicle will you
be in?
Don't know. habibi. don't know. Bye.
He's got nine lives.
Thank you.
Did you talk to them?
- Yes.
Who did you talk to?
With Uncle Khaled.
All right.
Ready for the operation?
Ready.
Very good.
Inshallah you'll get to see him this
afternoon.
Inshallah.
- Inshallah.
Anne.
Are you okay?
- Yes. I'm okay.
Very good. Come on. let's go.
Yael. put up a visual
of the "Al-Quds" school for me.
That's them. Those are the vehicles.
We can't take our eyes off them.
Dana. they're leaving.
Dana. they're splitting up.
Stay on the white Kia.
Here at... I'm near the farm.
so I went down
to buy something to eat.
What about Michael? - He's good.
I'm just dropping him off at basketball.
One second.
Wait. Anat. I'll call you right back.
It's Gabi. okay? A minute. - Okay. bye.
Talk to me.
Doron made contact.
I don't believe you.
Five vehicles left Tubas
into Israeli territory.
Danino's on his way to you.
And Steve. no one dies today.
that's an order.
We've paid enough.
Son of a bitch.
Cobra from Masada.
- This is Cobra. go ahead.
Copy. white Kangoo heading toward you
from the east on Route 505.
- Roger. copy.
Guys. prepare to dismount.
Bareket from Masada.
- Go ahead. Masada.
Burgundy Daihatsu moving
from Tubas heading to the coordinate.
Copy. 50 seconds and we're at the target.
It says here Herzl Pinto. Is that you?
You're a clown. huh?
So what? Is your crazy friend alive?
- Alive. yes.
Yalla. let's drive
before we lose him. - Yalla.
Drive.
We've located four cells so far.
We've sent forces there.
Did you get a Predator up? - Yes.
but until we locate Doron.
we can't take out any vehicle.
Those are two of the suspect vehicles.
If the fighters confirm the vehicle is clean.
we neutralize from the air.
Naama. Cobra and Bareket are a minute
from contact.
Go. go. go. go.
Team. go.
Masada. this is Cobra.
Copy. I'm at the coordinate.
Cobra copy. the target will be at your location in a moment.
You have a Predator for backup
if the agent isn't in the vehicle. - Copy.
Cobra. half a minute from contact.
I only see a driver.
Fire!
Masada. is there authorization for the Predator?
Cobra. is the vehicle clean? Over.
- Affirmative. the vehicle is clean.
Engage.
- Roger.
Bareket 2 from 1. positioning to check.
Team. go. go.
Masada from Bareket.
copy. I'm at the point. - Copy.
Bareket. be advised.
half a minute more to you.
Yalla. stop.
If the vehicle is without our agent.
you take it out.
Fire!
Cease fire.
Go. charge!
Masada from Bareket.
Go ahead. Bareket.
- Copy. one hostile in the vehicle neutralized.
The vehicle appears clean.
Masada. copy. I'm closing in on the vehicle
to do a sweep.
Masada. this is Cobra.
- Go ahead. Cobra.
Copy. I see one body in the vehicle.
What is this? Where's Doron?
What the hell is going on here?
Can you stop?
Can't.
Stop.
Stop. I'm about to throw up.
- I can't.
I'm about to throw up. stop.
Stop.
Drink. - Thanks.
Drink.
Dana. we stopped the Kia.
We sent the driver for interrogation.
Good. maybe we'll understand what's going on here.
Bat. the target stopped near a gas station.
Get there urgently.
Copy. Three minutes.
Well. what happened?
- Give her a moment.
We don't have time. We have to get
out of here fast. the army will arrive soon.
Get back in the car.
Get her into the car now.
- Jamil!
I'll be okay. Let's move.
Yalla.
Get back. back. - Move them back.
- Back now.
What's going on?
We got a report about the suspect
Chevrolet. It's back there.
A civilian saw a suspicious man running toward
the container on the right. - Got it.
Okay. we're going to clear the
vehicle. you stay here for cover
and get everyone out of here now.
We're at a fucking gas station.
Get out.
Drive. Fire.
Masada from Bat.
- What about the vehicle?
The suspect Chevrolet is cleared.
- Copy.
How many were there?
- The vehicle is clean. I repeat. the vehicle is clean.
What about Doron?
- Negative. he wasn't in the vehicle.
The Kia was empty too.
Gabi. we urgently need to get a location
from the interrogation of her driver.
Masada from Bat. there's a suspected hostile
barricaded in a container.
Copy. Wait in place for the negotiation team.
What do you say. Herzl?
A container.
Are you sure?
You don't want to wait?
- I don't want to wait for anyone.
We don't negotiate with him.
We take him out here and now.
But you heard them. Herzl...
Allahu Akbar!
Damn it.
Steve. what's going on?
One terrorist armed with a knife.
No sign of Doron.
What about the Outlander?
Have we found it yet? - Not yet.
We sent alerts to all the checkpoints.
Yeah. we're here right now. I don't...
I don't know when I'll be back.
They're not letting anyone go home.
Okay. I'll talk to you later. alright?
Bye.
What happened. Danino?
What did the rock ever do to you?
Herzl. tell me. what...
What was the rush to breach the container alone?
Why didn't we wait for reinforcements?
- Are you still there in the container. huh?
What did you think would happen. huh?
That we'd sit there drying out until the negotiation team arrives?
And then what? - Don't know.
Maybe if we hadn't riddled him with holes.
we could've gotten some
intelligence out of him.
Did you think about that?
Don't be a child. Danino.
Herzl. I'm a child. fine.
but I also know that now
we're sitting here with our dicks in our hands.
not knowing where our next
smack in the face will come from.
and maybe the son of a bitch in the container
would've given us something
instead of becoming
just another notch on the gun.
Is that what you think?
That I'm still looking to rack up kills?
You really are a child. huh?
- Then why go for the kill?
Come on. open my eyes.
- Instincts.
It's something that comes with age.
Fuck you. - Danino.
Danino. come. come here. come.
They didn't know anything. okay?
Understand?
They caught one of the drivers
of the suspect cars
and he said they sent them
to be bait
and we fucking took the bait.
How are you so sure?
- I talked to Ayoub.
Instincts. I told you.
You'll get there someday.
You didn't know there's a checkpoint here?
Listen.
You're tourists. I'm your guide.
Okay?
We came from Ramallah.
we're on the way to Arafat's tomb.
There's one here...
Where to?
Who's that?
We'll sleep at the "Peace" hostel.
Remember that.
Anne.
Yes. I understand.
I'll handle everything.
Just stay calm.
Tiger stations from Two. copy.
we've identified the suspect vehicle here.
I don't like this.
Something's wrong.
Get ready.
Guys. I'll count to three.
One. two... what are you doing?
Why the delay?
Get back in the car.
- Huh? Why the delay?
Get on the ground!
- Okay. okay.
And hands up!
- Calm down.
Hands up! Hands up!
- What's he doing?
Listen carefully.
my name is Doron Kabilio.
I'm from Unit 61.
What's your name?
- Tomer.
Tomer. I'm standing up now. okay?
Don't shoot.
You got information
about the vehicle behind me. right?
There are two suicide bombers there
and an armed driver.
Is your pistol loaded?
- Yes.
I'm going to use it.
Tell all the soldiers around you not
to shoot and only to cover us. Go.
Tiger stations. listen.
we've identified the suspect vehicle here.
There's an undercover operative here
running the incident.
No one shoots without an order.
Now listen to me carefully.
Ready?
Push me.
It's time.
Switch to active mode now.
It's the other side.
Give me a push.
Turn me around.
Release me over there.
Don't shoot. - Don't shoot. Cease fire.
Cease fire. don't shoot.
- Get out of the vehicle! Get out of the vehicle!
No one shoots.
Don't do anything.
- Call a bomb tech.
Don't do anything. Let go of it.
Give it to me.
It's okay. it's okay.
It's okay.
Get me a bomb tech.
Hello.
- Gabi.
Thank God.
Turn around. Hands.
Are you okay?
- Yes. Did you stop the cells?
Gabi. talk to me.
The vehicles were empty.
He sent all kinds of idiots who didn't
even understand where we came down on them from.
They're on the way to the Western Wall.
We have to stop them.
They're not at the Western Wall and they won't get there.
- What? What are you talking about?
We interrogated the Kia's driver.
It was a diversion.
He played you. Doron.
He played all of us.
Get to the facility. I'll update you.
Brought. fixed and synced by:
Yoav1610
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm